[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
Tear a piece off.
- Tear a piece off.
- There.
- Give it to me.
- Here, you eat it.
Here.
You eat it.
Here, bro.
You eat it. I'm not hungry.
Uh...
Well...
That... That's too kind of you.
It's all ours.
We'll save it for tomorrow.
Is the fuel line fixed?
No.
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
Lin Zai.
[Apocalypse Log 8]
I'm going to look for more diesel.
This sleeve...
How did it get torn?
I must have snagged it somewhere.
It's fine.
How can it be fine?
Come, let me stitch it up for you.
It's fine, madam. Really.
It'll be quick.
You silly child.
If your family were here,
and saw you running around
in these torn clothes,
they would feel so heartbroken.
If I were your mother,
just thinking about you out there,
not eating or dressing well,
with no one to look after you...
It would feel like
countless needles pricking my heart.
In this world, nothing is more important
than your own safety.
You have to take care of yourself.
Do you understand?
Look.
It's all sewn up.
Is the boat fixed?
Is the boat being fixed all you care about now?
We have to leave as soon as possible.
Leave as soon as possible...
And then what?
Is there anything else on your mind right now
besides your damn mission?
There is.
Getting to HQ as soon as possible
is best for everyone.
Everyone?
So, you still see me as just an immune, huh?
If I weren't an immune,
you'd just leave me to die, right?
I...
Fine.
Very well.
I get it.
We just need some fuel.
Madam.
Do you know where the nearest town is?
There's one five kilometers east.
What's wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
No.
Isn't your son injured?
I was wondering where to get supplies
if we ran out of medicine.
You're so kind.
Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
Hey!
Someone, help!
What's wrong with you?
What happened to him?
I...
He just ate a little of that.
I gathered some wild herbs and fruits
and mashed them into a paste.
He's allergic to this.
How... How is that possible?
Where's the medicine?
I wouldn't dare touch your things.
Right.
There should be medicine in town.
Five kilometers to the east.
You should leave him here.
We'll help you look after him.
There are zombies in town.
It's not convenient to carry him.
We'll watch over him for you.
Go and come back quickly.
Watch him.
Give him plenty of water
and keep his airway clear.
When I get back,
if even a single hair
on his head is missing...
Don't worry.
We'll definitely take good care of him.
Come back soon.
This is a real godsend.
Go and get ready.
When that kid comes back,
we'll catch him off guard.
Mom, go back inside.
Keep a close eye on that one.
Don't let anything go wrong.
I know.
Go.
You... You're awake.
Thanks. I'll be going now.
That won't do.
That young man told us to watch over you.
I'm really fine now. I'm leaving.
If you leave, what are we supposed to do?
When that young man returns,
he'll kill us if he doesn't see you.
He's not the type to kill innocents.
Quick! Stop him!
Meat.
Eat meat.
My poor child.
It's your mother's fault.
Since you were little,
I haven't been able to give you much meat.
I've failed you.
Mom.
Don't keep saying that.
Didn't a tender one just arrive?
How should we handle this one?
For Cheng Cai, take a thigh.
And the ribs.
Chop them off.
Make some rib soup.
As for the rest, marinate it.
It'll last us for a while.
Cheng Cai.
It's about time.
Go lie in wait for the other one.
Be careful.
That one is tough.
Meat.
- Meat.
- Be careful.
Cheng Ren.
Go and get that kid.
Let go of me!
Son!
Son! Let go of my son!
Let go of my son!
No one can hurt my son!
Mom.
Mom!
Don't.
Don't kill me.
I'm a human being.
Lin Zai.